<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zach Bouzan Kaloustian</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zach Bouzan Kaloustian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:51:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on 2019 and Looking Ahead at 2020</title>
      <link>/blog/reflecting_on_2019_and_looking_ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:51:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/reflecting_on_2019_and_looking_ahead/</guid>
      <description>An Idea for a Company I spent a lot of time in the fall of 2019 thinking through the idea of building a bespoke outsourcing company for startups. The idea was to eventually compete on the higher-end, aka not on cost, with highly trained and skilled knowledge workers while doing the work overseas and/or remotely from the US (Remote is such an attractive model btw!).
In the research process I spoke to a number of really experienced people who have all been involved in delivering, enhancing, or consuming support services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you pay $0.38 to ripen your avocado?</title>
      <link>/blog/avocado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:22:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/avocado/</guid>
      <description>Would you pay $0.38 to ripen your avocado? Of course you would, and here&#39;s how to make it happen.
The typical story of any millennials life is that they go to Trader Joe&#39;s [Whole Foods, Piggly Wiggly] with the intention of making delicious toast. Inevitably, they find rock hard avocados that resemble bowling balls instead of tender ripe fruit.
Not to worry, pick up those rocks (avocados) and 2 bananas - which cost $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Wow</title>
      <link>/blog/findwow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 14:22:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/findwow/</guid>
      <description>Find wow! In the past week I had two experiences that gave me chills. One way at a free exhibit and another at a Broadway show. The African photos
Stillness to find wow in everyday life. Put away your phone to find it.
Find it in everyday circumstances, like the work of a great teammate or the love of your partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Zach</title>
      <link>/blog/aboutzach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 14:22:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/aboutzach/</guid>
      <description>Quick Bio Zach is an Operations and Customer Experience leader with twelve years of experience building international, customer-centric service organizations. He&#39;s based in NYC where he lives with his fabulous wife. You can find him around town eating well, working out, taking photos, or on a travel adventure.
Zach&#39;s superpowers  Customer-centricity: The customer is at the heart of how my teams operate, how we train, and how we think. Their happiness and success leads to our success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>